# 无论身处何处 快乐永远同在 #
Wherever we are, there's fun to be found
# 转过街角 我们同在 #
We'll be there when you turn that corner
# 带着大大的熊笑 跳出树丛 #
When you jump out the bush
# 我们同在 #
With a big bear hug and a smile
We'll be there
兄弟
等级制度
Hierarchy
一般存在于三人及以上的组织里
ofter within a group of three or more,
有个领导者 否则组织会出问题
organization is difficult unless there is a leader.
等级制度是权力高低的次序
Hierarchy is a ranking of authority.
通常团队中的一个成员
Often when one member of the group
比较年长 更强壮 或者更有经验
is older, stronger, or more experienced,
他们会理所当然的扮演保护者的身份
they will naturally assume the role of the protector
这是等级制度的上层
at the top of the hierarchy.
但是如果有人本是下层等级 想变成上层
But what happens when someone at the bottom of the hierarchy